Hello hello friends namaste welcome to all of you
in today's video today's video is going to be
very helpful if you have
bought any Hero bike and its stupidity has reduced then for that
because we are
not able to put Hero's brain at all
if my copy has become old then for that
you have to go to the province itself, it is
available to your pimples, it is
nutritious for the body also from Manipal, I am
not talking about the same thing if you have a 5 year
policy then how
can you download it and not only and not only about the
bike, sorry so friends
let's start how can you
download it this is the Hero website from
where you get rid of it, so
I will put its link in the description box
after clicking from there also you
can come here, so whatever we have done is to
ignore your policy, click on
download policy copy, before clicking here
you have to have your phone
number and your mobile number, only then
you can download this policy
and in this also it is very important to register between your email ID  It is very
important, so
friends let's start downloading and
after clicking on this topic, you have to
enter the policy number here, so we enter
our policy number, whatever portion number you have,
you have to enter it here,
you have to enter it only then you will be
able to get your policy, that is,
enter it here
and after that you have to enter your
registered mobile number which you have just registered with your policy
SIM, you have to
enter the same policy mobile number here, if you
enter the second mobile number then it will invite you here,
click on St. Paul School pickup,
ghee, then your fans will get any
military
leader not exist in the system for this
system, if anyone is found on this then we
cannot send him to you, so for that you
should do that, then you will get it yourself, if
this work is not done then you
click on subscribe tab, it will open in front of you
and you send all your details there
and if something happens then you will grind it
and your body will be sent to you,
wherever you go, your work will be done
sitting at home, so friends,
by following this policy  You can also get your policy,
so friends, if you
liked this video then please like, share and subscribe,
thank you friends
[Music]